A Guide to the Governor James Patton Preston Executive Papers, 1816-1819
Library of Virginia
Arrangement
Arranged chronologically by date of document with pardons and undated items arranged to the rear.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Bibliography
Flournoy, H. W., CALENDAR OF VIRGINIA STATE PAPERS, January 1, 1808-December 31, 1835, VOL. X, Richmond: James E. Goode, Printer, 1892.
Contents List
- James Patton Preston Executive Papers
- 1816
  - December
    - 12-31 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 1817
  - January
    - 2-15 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 16-31 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - February
    - 1-27 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - March
    - 1-14 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 16-29 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - April
    - 1-15 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 16-30 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - May
    - 1-15 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 16-31 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - June
    - 1-10 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - 11-20 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - 21-30 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - July
    - 1-10 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - 11-20 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - 21-30 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - August
    - 1-15 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - 16-30 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - September
    - 1-30 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - October
    - 4-25 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - 27-31 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - November
    - 1-20 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - 23-30 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - December
    - 1-11 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - 12-25 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 26-31 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Pardons
    - C-G (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - H-W (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
- 1818
  - January
    - 1-15 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - 16-31 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - February
    - 1-14 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - 16-28 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - March
    - 1-15 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - 16-31 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - April
    - 1-10 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - 11-20 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - 21-31 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - May
    - 1-15 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - 18-30 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - June
    - 1-10 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 10-20 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - 21-30 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - July
    - 1-10 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - 11-20 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - 21-31 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - August
    - 1-13 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - 14-30 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - September
    - 1-15 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - 16-29 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - October
    - 1-15 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - 16-31 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - November
    - 2-20 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - 23-30 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - December
    - 1-15 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - 16-31 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Pardons (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
- 1819
  - January
    - 1-15 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - 16-31 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - February
    - 1-15 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - 16-28 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - March
    - 1-15 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - 16-20 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - 22-31 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - April
    - 1-15 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - 19-30 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - May
    - 1-15 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - 17-31 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - June
    - 1-12 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - 14-20 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - 21-27 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - 28-30 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - July
    - 1-10 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 11-20 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - 21-31 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - August
    - 2-15 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - 16-31 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - September
    - 2-15 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - 16-30 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - October
    - 1-13 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - 16-31 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - November
    - 1-10 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - 11-20 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - 22-30 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - December
    - 1-10 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Pardons
    - A-K (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - M-W (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Oversized (Clamshell Box)
  - 1816
    - Dec. 13 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 1817
    - Aug. 5 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Sept. 13 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Dec. 1 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 1818
    - March 16 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - June [N.D.] (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - July 17 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Aug. 15 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Oct. 10 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Oct. 10 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Nov. 3 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Dec. 23 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - 1819
    - Jan. 1 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Jan. 8 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - June 7 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Sept. 24 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Oct. 1 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Oct. 1 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Oct. 17 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Oct. 27 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Oct. 30 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Nov. 11 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Nov. 24 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Pardons
      - Beuner, Jacob, et al. (Box 10, Folder 24)
      - Smith, Munford (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Oversized (Newspaper Box)
  - 1817
    - Dec. 31 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 1818
    - Jan. 10 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Jan. 28 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - June 25 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 1819
    - Jan. 6 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - July 31 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Nov. 8 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Dec. 7 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Pardons
      - Jennings, Presley (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Mingo (slave) (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Woodford, Thomas (Box 11, Folder 11)